(pain shriek)
[Mahito] Ahh!
There you are!
-(laughs)
-Hm?
Jougo!
(laughs)
(unhappy grumble)
I see you have most
of your body back.
Yeah, this is a good
place to rejuvenate.
Humans don't come
anywhere near it.
[Mahito] Not having a
body really sucks, huh?
It makes self-preservation
so difficult.
Mahito.
You should know, you're
awfully worn down yourself.
Oh, you can tell?
It turns out Sukuna and his
vessel are my natural enemies.
I started this whole game
because I happened
to acquire a new toy.
It was great at first but
then it didn't work out.
Should've used a hostage.
Then I could've forced
him into a pact, am I right?
Hand your body over to Sukuna,
if you don't want to
see this dude killed!
(aggravated growl)
You failed, because
pacts are only ever placed
by oneself on oneself.
It's not easy to forge
pacts with others,
because of
intervention from others.
[Mahito] Maybe I
should have just given
that thing a lethal wound,
instead of transfiguring it.
Then Sukuna might
have been able to heal it
with his reverse
cursed technique.
Don't forget your place.
Foolish puppet.
No, not with that personality.
I think he would have
refused either way.
Jougo?
Touching Sukuna made me realize
that we should probably
proceed with Getou's plan, for now.
Sukuna is that valuable.
(suspicious grumble)
You mean gather all the fingers
and offer them to Sukuna, huh?
Even if that means we all get
wiped out in the process, eh?
Very well then.
I sure don't intend to
be the one left laughing
like a lunatic in the
wasteland a century from now.
As long as curses exist as
people that's all that matters.
Oh!
You understand exactly!
Good, then first we
need to go retrieve
the six fingers
from Jujutsu Tech.
Do we have to?
I thought the sorcerers
were only keeping
Yuuji Itadori around
so that he can swallow
Sukuna's fingers.
If we leave him alone
he'll still eat them.
The higher-ups at Jujutsu Tech
are still trying to calculate
Yuuji Itadori's
strength as a vessel.
They want to see just how
many fingers he can take.
They want to
gather all the fingers
and then have him consume them.
With just one exception.
"Exception"
I want him to eat them all, now!
But we can't just wait around.
Worst case, there's the
chance they could decide
to eliminate Yuuji Itadori.
So into the tiger's
den we go, huh?
Then just how do you
think we oughta proceed?
Already started.
My first move was
allowing Jujutsu Tech
to retrieve the fingers we had.
(opening theme music)
"Jujutsu Kaisen"
"Episode 14:
"Kyoto Sister School Exchange
Event - Group Battle 0-"
Nanami!
Come on, would you
say something interesting!
(light exasperated grunt)
Okay!
I've got it! Yeah!
We'll record us playing
catch with a stale rice ball!
While discussing
economic policies!
Then we'll post a
video and go trolling!
You can enjoy that on your own.
What kind of idea is that?
A drinking game then!
Name all the things you
like about Satoru Gojou!
See who names the most!
My turn.
Everything!
You just keep on
thinking that way.
It's totally idiotic,
but Itadori needs that
kind of idiocy right now.
You'll be sent out on
more difficult missions.
To be honest though,
that wasn't the kind
of difficult I meant.
Nanami?
Does Yuuji know about that
finger in Junpei Yoshino's--
I haven't told him.
Knowing Yuuji, he'd just
feel unnecessarily responsible.
I'm glad I left you
in charge of him.
So, where is it now?
I submitted it to the
higher-ups, of course.
If I gave it to you,
you would've already
fed it to Itadori.
Ouch.
But...
Are you really sure that
it's safe to bring him back?
If they find out he's alive
at the exchange event,
won't the higher-ups
just target him again?
Even if they do
Yuuji will be fine now.
You know that better
than anyone, don't you?
(sigh)
Hey! Gojou!
(laugh)
Oh, Nanami's here too!
Well come on guys!
Let's hurry up, I
wanna go see everyone!
I can't wait!
Can't wait!
It's so exciting!
I'm so pumped!
Yuuji? What are you thinking?
After all this time,
you can just show up
like nothing happened?
(shock gasp) I can't?
Even among sorcerers it's rare
to essentially come
back from the dead
after being gone for
like two whole months.
So we have to
make it a surprise!
A surprise, how?
[Gojou] You just
leave all that to me!
Huh?
[Gojou] The first-years will be
crying and laughing
from happiness and shock.
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
[Gojou] The second-years
and Kyoto students
will cry with them,
and someone will
choke up and vomit!
(vomiting)
And in the end, it'll even
solve global warming!
[] Cool!
So cool!
So, what's my
job in this, tell me!
What do I have to do here?
You don't have to
do anything, Yuuji.
You just do exactly as I
say and go with the flow!
Hey I can do that!
I can go with the flow!
[Nanami] It'll be enough
of a surprise for them
just to see he's alive.
Hey!
Why are you guys
all empty-handed?
[All] Hm?
Where do you think you're
going with all that luggage?
Wait a sec.
Aren't we all traveling today?
For the exchange event with
our sister school in Kyoto?
Yes it's an exchange event
with our sister school in Kyoto.
Here in Tokyo.
No freaking way!
That explains why she hasn't
been making any sense lately.
No doubt.
Salmon.
The previous year's
winner always hosts it.
So why'd you have
to go and win it?
It wasn't us! We weren't
even in it last year!
They just put in Yuuta so
the numbers would match up!
Yeah 'cause that was
before Rika got freed.
Apparently, it was
an overwhelming win,
but I didn't get to see it
since it was held in Kyoto.
I'll never forgive
you Yuuta Okkotsu!
Even though in fact,
I've never met you!
Misdirected rage.
-Salmon.
-Hm?
Hey.
Here they come.
Oh damn.
The whole Tokyo
crowd all together, huh?
You actually came to greet us?
So amateur.
"Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto
Second-Year Zenin Mai"
I don't see Okkotsu though.
"Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto
Third-Year Toudou Aoi"
Oh shut your mouth already
and hand over the cake box.
And the yatsuhashi,
noodles and cookies.
Salmon.
[Aoi] What, are you guys hungry?
Whoa, who is that first year?
Badass.
"Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto
Third-Year Nishimiya Momo"
Never mind Okkotsu's absence,
isn't fielding two
first-years a major handicap?
[Nobara] Oh, it's
a freaking robot!
"Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto
Second-Year Ultimate Mechamaru"
With sorcerers,
physical age is irrelevant.
"Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto
Third-Year Kamo Noritoshi"
Especially with him.
Fushiguro's from the Zenin
bloodline, but he's talented.
More so even than
the head of the clan.
(miffed grunt)
Comment?
Not here.
Now now, you two!
Save all that for
the event okay?
"Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto
Second-Year Miwa Kasumi"
Okay now, let's not fight
amongst ourselves alright?
My goodness, these children.
"Jujutsu Tech,
Semi-First-Grade Sorcerer
"Kyoto School
Leader Iori Utahime"
Now...
Where's that idiot?
Satoru's running late.
As if that idiot ever
shows up on time.
No one said idiot
specifically referred to Gojou.
[All] Hm?
Sorry for the wait!
Hmph.
-Satoru Gojou!
Glad to see everyone
all gathered together!
I'm just getting back from a
big ol' business trip overseas!
So now it's time to
hand out the souvenirs!
This is sudden.
Sure it's not jet lag?
'Kay, everybody from Kyoto
gets this tribal
protective charm doll.
Except you Utahime.
I don't want one!
And now, for all of you
Tokyo peeps I have this!
Ta-da!
It's creepy when
adults get all excited.
Hey!
Opapi!
It's your long-dead
friend Yuuji!
(grossed-out horror gasp reax)
Hey!
What the hell?
What kind of reaction is this?
They don't seem
happy to see me at all!
N-No way...
Alrighty then.
Everyone from Kyoto, this is
Sukuna's vessel, Yuuji Itadori!
W-What?
The Kyoto guys
aren't impressed either!
They're all too absorbed
in their little souvenirs!
Sukuna's vessel lives?
Just who is behind this outrage?
"Jujutsu Tech, Kyoto School
Principal Gakuganji Yoshinobu"
Huh?
Oh Principal Gakuganji!
Thank goodness you're all right.
I was worried when you saw him
that you might just
keel right over dead.
You know, from the shock.
You insolent damn brat!
(mocking laughter)
Hey.
Uh, yeah?
You got something
you wanna say to us?
Uh...
(squirming)
(fuming)
I'm sorry that I didn't tell you
I was still alive all this time?
"Itadori Rejoins"
"Jujutsu Kaisen"
"Jujutsu Technical High School
"Tokyo-Kyoto Sister
School Exchange Event"
The Tokyo-Kyoto Sister
School Exchange Event
will be held over two days.
The first day is a group
battle: Exorcism Race!
The Wacky Cursed
Spirit Exorcism Race!
The rules are simple.
The first team to exorcise
the second-grade cursed spirit
released in the
designated area wins.
Several third-grade
and lower cursed spirits
will be released into the
designated area as well.
If a winner is not
decided by sundown
then the team that
exorcises the most wins.
There are absolutely
no other rules.
Of course, you're welcome
to sabotage the others.
But remember, you're
all on the same side
in the fight against the curses.
This exchange
event will allow you
to learn about yourselves,
and your comrades,
through competition.
Be certain at all times not
to kill other competitors
or needlessly injure
them beyond recovery.
(snickering)
That's it!
You're all dismissed until
the event commences at noon!
"Tokyo Side Meeting"
Uhh, guys?
Depending on how you
look at the situation here,
what you're doing could be
considered extreme bullying.
Shut up.
I think you've said enough.
Now now...
You heard his explanation.
We should cut him some slack.
A talking panda?
Salmon salmon.
Say what?
Inumaki is a cursed-speech user.
His speech amplifies the
power and compulsion of words.
He limits his vocabulary
to keep others safe.
So if he told someone
to go die they'd do it?
Awesome.
It's nothing quite that simple.
It always varies, depending
on the opponent's strengths.
Using powerful words can
produce massive feedback.
Worst case it can
affect him as well.
Limiting his vocabulary
is a way for Toge
to protect himself and others.
Ahh...
So, how is it you can speak?
Are you a new breed of panda?
Stop being so nosy about
everyone else's techniques!
It's fine.
Toge's ability's no big secret.
More importantly, Yuuji...
Huh?
Hand over my blade!
You borrowed Slaughter
Demon from Satoru, right?
Uh oh...
Gimme that.
Here you go!
I uhh...
You jerks!
(fright, trembling)
Gojou has it.
Last I saw it.
The blindfolded dumbass!
Hmm...
(alarmed inhale)
That was disgusting.
So, what's our new plan?
Our group battle plan
is what we expected,
but we have another member now.
Should we change strategies?
We don't have much time.
Bonito flakes.
Well I think that'll
depend on Yuuji.
What are your specialties?
Punch, kick--
We're already pretty
well set for all of that.
Huh?
I don't know what
he's been doing,
since he's been
dead for a while now.
But I can say this much,
if we all fought him
without cursed energy
Itadori'd still beat us.
[Both] Oh?
Megumi's saying that,
even after fighting Toudou?
That makes it pretty convincing.
Interesting!
"Kyoto Side Meeting"
You must kill Yuuji Itadori!
Sukuna's vessel is
not an actual person.
So the act will go unquestioned.
Without a doubt the entire event
will be seen as an accident.
So there's no need for
you to hold back or hesitate.
I don't want to!
You're telling us to kill him.
But he's only here because
he didn't die the last time.
I've been told that
Itadori's previous death
was by suicide.
Kamo?
When ending a hostile sorcerer,
what is the one thing you
must be cautious about?
Sir.
So that they don't
come back as a curse
you must kill them
with cursed energy.
Yes, correct.
As long as one of you
delivers the finishing blow
using cursed energy
all will be well.
For now, Yuuji Itadori
seems to have full
control over his body.
So unless Sukuna comes out,
the boy is just
another first-year.
Which means that
killing him will be--
This sucks!
Do what you want.
Hold on, Toudou.
The principal
hasn't finished yet.
Takada will be making
a live appearance
on a TV show today at eleven.
And I am not gonna miss that.
You can record it.
Come back.
I'm gonna watch it in real
time and I'm gonna record it!
What kinda fool
d'you think I am?
That's what you're
worried about?
You all listen up!
And you too, old man!
I've been putting up
with all of your failures
and your lousy taste in
women for long enough!
So you can plot and scheme
all you want on your own.
But now, if you try to
order me around again,
I will kill you!
So what do we do now?
How are we gonna
carry out the game plan
with Toudou acting like that?
Now the principal's
gone off too.
Personally, I really don't
want to be killed by that guy.
Does it even matter?
Toudou's just going
to charge head-first
into the Tokyo team anyway.
So I figure while
he goes berserk
the rest of us can
just keep our efforts
focused on the game.
Don't forget we have direct
orders to kill Yuuji Itadori.
We're seriously doing this?
Honestly, I doubt Toudou
will actually kill him.
But he is capable of it.
Then we'll need
to assign someone
to keep an eye on Toudou,
and deliver the final
blow to Yuuji Itadori.
I don't like this.
Because of the cursed spirits
we'll all be in two-man cells.
So that works for us.
No.
Allowing a half-wit
like Yuuji Itadori
to exist as a sorcerer at this
school is a serious problem.
One that goes beyond this event.
As Kamo clan elder I decree,
it must end.
We will all attack
Itadori together.
Hold on.
What if Toge Inumaki is there
with Itadori when we attack?
Having all of us in one
place is a risky move
with that cursed speech user.
Worst case, he could
wipe us all out at once.
She has a point.
No.
If you know he's coming,
he's not that difficult to handle.
Let me take care of
Maki and while I'm at it
that brown-haired
first year as well.
What's on your mind?
You're starting to
sound like Toudou.
(growl)
Well then?
What did you want?
Huh?
Are you upset now?
No I'm not upset at all.
'Course not.
'Cause I haven't
done anything wrong.
(irritated growl)
But I'm afraid we have a spy.
Someone's working with a curse
-or a curse user here.
-(gasp)
Impossible!
A curse user's one thing,
but working with curses?
And yet a lot of
them on that level
have been popping up lately.
They understand human speech,
and they've formed a faction
that's operating with purpose.
They might think
they're just working
with a curse user, but...
You need to investigate
everyone at Kyoto.
For all you know I could
be the traitor so why me?
Ohh no way!
You're too weak.
You don't have
the guts for that.
Ooh! Hysterics are a
turnoff for men, you know.
[Utahime] That's enough!
I'm the senior in charge here!
[Megumi] Itadori.
Hmm?
You okay?
Yeah, but I've got a
big job, from what I hear.
I mean about what happened.
Ha, no, nothing happened!
'Kay, yeah.
Something did happen.
But it's true that I'm okay.
In fact, because of it I
really don't want to lose.
Alright then.
Huh?
Because I don't
wanna lose either.
Why're you two
talking about losing?
After you already
got rolled once!
Whoa! Let's go!
Let's kick their asses!
Let's do it for Maki!
Don't say stuff like that.
Pollack roe.
Yeah! Let's do it for Maki!
[Maki] I said, don't
say stuff like that!
In that case...
Let's win!
(grunt)
Who said you could go first?
(ending theme music)
Juju Stroll!
"Sushi Eishuu"
Hi!
Today we're at the
famous sushi restaurant
known as Sushi Eishuu!
You should dress
like that and be on TV.
You know you'd be
mad at me if I did that.
[Sushi Chef] Welcome
to Sushi Eishuu.
So what would you like, Takada?
What's your favorite?
I really love goatfish!
And room-temperature sake!
They go great together!
Uhh, just how old are you?
Huh?
How long have you
been making sushi, boss?
Since I was 20 years old.
Which I guess probably
means about 300 years?
Are you drunk?
[Sushi Chef] Here.
Enjoy your goatfish.
Mmm!
Ohhh, mmm!
That is so good!
Can I have yours, too?
No, of course you can't.
[Takada] Oh, I'm sorry!
[Man In Blue Suit] Honestly,
what are you thinking?
Well, it just looked
-She' probably is drunk.
-so delicious!
That's my girl Takada.
Did you know OPP actually
stands for something?
Yeah?
Like what?
[Yuuji] Ocean Pacific Peace
[Gojou] Seriously?
(intense music)
"Episode 15: Kyoto Sister
School Exchange Event -
"Group Battle 1-"